All right, now the second
point I want to make
is that there's a mistake
on tomorrow's quiz,
just in the schedule.
So quiz number
eight will be given
at the beginning of class.
Quiz eight is at beginning
of class, not the end.
I think it might
mistakenly say the end.
So you might notice
sometimes the quiz--
so tomorrow the quiz is going to
cover defects and then whatever
was covered up until Monday's
lecture and Tuesday's
recitation, which includes
the beginning of what
we talked about--
[DINGING]
OK, let's not do that.
Let's turn that off.
And we had an exam on a
Monday, and so we didn't want
to give you a quiz that week.
So we're doing defects tomorrow
even though we covered defects
last week.
And then we didn't want
to give you a quiz right
before or on Thanksgiving.
That didn't seem right.
So for the next quiz
what we're doing is
we're still making a
quiz for you to have,
and we're going to give
it to you next week
but we're not going to count it.
So next week you
will still get a quiz
that you have for your studying
because I know you'll miss it.
But in case you're
not here or you
don't want to do the
quiz over your turkey,
we're not going
to count that one.
So quiz nine won't be counted.
All right, so
that's the quizzes.